朱姆沃尔特级驱逐舰
【注：实验中的美国海军驱逐舰 设计为多任务功能近海攻击舰与神盾防御舰】
The Zumwalt-class destroyer.
展现了美国海军
Demanding the best from the Navy
及其建造公司的最佳水平
and the companies constructing her.
你们四位代表着下一波
You four represent the next wave
能够提高我们军人生活质量的
of U.S. defense companies
美国防务公司
who will improve the lives of our military personnel
让他们更加安全 更好地武装自己
by keeping them safer and better equipping them
从而来保护我们大家
to defend us.
各位 携手同行
Gentlemen, together...
我们就是美国海军的未来
we are the future of the United States Navy.
海军部长Porter女士
Madam Secretary Porter,
为什么我们公司的标志比Marc的小
why is my logo smaller than Marc's?
Beringer Marine今年
Beringer Marine laid down a million tons
制造了一百万吨的原钢
of raw steel this year.
而United Equinox(优耐电子)只做了一枚小螺丝钉
United Equinox made a tiny screw.
我们是做了一枚很小很小的螺丝钉
we made a teeny, tiny screw
这枚螺丝钉能承受1200度的
that could withstand a 1,200 degree
温度变化
temperature swing.
而且我们做了一大堆这样的螺丝钉
And we made a crap-ton of them.
这是另一个戏剧般的环节吗 McGee
Is this another dramatic touch, McGee?
不是的 部长女士
Not exactly, Madam Secretary.
网络安全技术检测到一个
Network security detected
未经授权的电子传输设备
an unauthorized electronic transmission.
所有程序都自动终止了
Everything shuts down automatically.
有黑客试图从外部入侵吗
Does that mean someone's trying to hack in from the outside?
不 只有内部攻击才会造成封锁
No. Lockdown only happens if the attack's internal.
威胁就在这个屋子里
The threat's in this room.
本字幕仅作学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业用途 否则后果自负
==GA字幕组==
翻译:小末 好想多点睡觉时间的冰糖 米兰伯爵 睡眠不够的小白
校对：失眠长痘的流年 佳晨就是good morning K穿学士服了 蓉小张要去旅游 lynhoo00 毯子
字幕特效/时间轴/压制：老东邪
我重看了《太空城》
【注：007系列的第11部】
I just reread Moonraker.
用了星期日一整天的时间
Spent the whole day reading on Sunday.
不记得上一次像这样是什么时候了
Don't remember the last time that happened.
你看过很多书吗
You read a lot?
你懂的 昨晚我出去喝了一杯
You know, I went out for a drink last night,
然后我遇到了一个女孩
and I met a girl.
她有着迷人的微笑 性感的身材
Great smile, great body.
猜猜看她是做什么工作的
Guess what she does for a living.
我在考虑做个变性手术 Norma
I'm thinking about getting a sex change, Norma.
你说什么了吗 DiNozzo探员
You say something,Agent DiNozzo?
我只是想找个话题和你聊聊
I'm just trying to make conversation.
-和我吗 -是的
- With me? - Yeah.
我根本没在听
I wasn't listening.
那我们重新开始
Start over.
真的吗
Really?
原来我是在和一个职业网球运动员约会
So, I guess it turns out that I'm dating a tennis pro.
想不想知道她是怎么给我电话号码的
Want to know how she gave me her number?
留在了她的枕头上
Boop! Left it on her pillow.
不错吧
Hello.
很不错
That's nice.
就这样吗
That's it?
你还想要怎样
What do you want?
你得给点反应啊
Well, a little something.
讥讽啊 嘲笑啊 鄙视的眼神什么的
Just a jibe, a scoff, a little stink-eye, you know?
我只是...我需要一点回应
I just... I need something.
哪怕你"呸"我一声也好
The riff, the pattere, the "pah."
噢 你刚刚鄙视了我一下 我看到了
Oh, you got a stink-eye in there. I can see it.
我只是需要那声"呸"
Listen, I just need the "pah."
McGee探员在哪里
Where's Agent McGee?
不应该把所有重担都交给Tim
The burden shouldn't always fall on Tim.
他承受得太多了
He's suffered enough.
Gibbs探员呢
What about Agent Gibbs?
嘿 老大 我在和一个职业网球运动员约会
Hey, boss, dating a tennis pro.
很不错啊
That's nice.
我们走
Let's go.
看到没
See?
又有案子了吗
We got a body?
是信息泄露
It's a breach.
我们不用开车去
We're not driving.
我们要去哪里
Where we going?
楼上
Upstairs.
发生了什么 Leon
What's happening, Leon?
在安全模式下
In secure mode,
MTAC的传感器不断扫描电子信号
MTAC sensors constantly scan for electronic signals.
如果除我们设备外的其它东西
Anything other than our equipment
发射无线电频率 房间就会被封锁
emits a radio frequency, room goes on lockdown.
在我们找到问题源头前 任何人都不能离开
Nobody's allowed to leave till we find the source.
可能是一个监视装置 或是窃听器
Like a surveillance device,a bug.
没错
Right.
-这种事经常发生吗 -不
- Does this happen a lot? - No.
把这种东西带进一个安全级别高的房间 可不是很聪明的做法
Not the brightest idea to bring one into a secure room.
所以他们要检查你两次 Marc
That's why they're gonna check you twice, Marc.
你省省吧 Ward
Save it, Ward.
这可不是开玩笑的时候
Not exactly the time.
都没有问题
All clear.
我扫描了每个角落 老大
I've scanned every square inch, boss.
无论是座位 墙壁 计算机操控台 都没有任何非法设备的痕迹
Seats, walls, computer console--no sign of any illicit devices.
-错误警报 软件故障 -可能是
- False alarm? Software glitch? - Possible.
这是不是表明 我们可以
Does that mean we're free to let
让我们重要的商业合作伙伴离开了 主任
our valued corporate partners go, Director?
可以解除封锁了 伙计们
You can take us off lockdown, fellas.
-是 长官 -先生们 请
- Yes, sir. - Gentlemen, please.
又是故障吗
Another malfunction?
我以为你检查过所有人了 DiNozzo探员
I thought you searched everyone, Agent DiNozzo.
我觉得你不会希望我们
I didn't think you wanted me to pat down
对美国的海军部长搜身吧 长官
the United States Secretary of the Navy, sir.
我现在倒是希望了
Well, I do now.
请张开双臂 女士
Uh, raise your arms, please, ma'am.
请记得 我还要养家糊口的
Just remember,I have mouths to feed.
两条金鱼
Two goldfish.
我是家里唯一的顶梁柱
I'm their only source of income,
并且它们 它们无比可爱
and they're-they're awfully cute.
放轻松 DiNozzo 我和你一样迫不及待
Relax, DiNozzo. I'm as anxious about this as you are.
我必须要检查下你的口袋 女士
I'm gonna have to search your pockets, ma'am.
你是否携带任何尖锐的东西
Do you have any needles or sharp objects?
我必须得问
I have to ask.
没有 你继续吧
No. Proceed.
一只笔
A pen?
我还真担心了一阵子呢 先生们
You had me worried for a moment, gentlemen.
这鬼东西是什么
The the hell's that?
第一印象 这是个闪存盘
Well, first impression,it's a flash drive
连接到一个针孔麦克风
connected to a pinhole microphone.
我们找到窃听器了
We got our bug.
我就是那个漏洞
I'm the breach.
我们先把话说明吧
Okay, let's clear the air right now.
我不知道是何时或何地得到这支笔的
I have no idea when or where I got that pen.
可能是在医生的办公室 银行 或者餐厅
Could have been a doctor's office, bank, restaurant.
我记得最后一次用它
The last time I remember using it
是昨天早上为我女儿
was when I signed a permission slip
签一份同意书的时候
for my daughter yesterday morning.
在那之后 我一定是把笔放进了口袋
And I must have put the pen in my pocket after that,
但我不知道它在录音
but I had no idea it was recording me.
好的
Okay.
你相信我的话
You believe that?
-是的 -为什么
- Yes. - Why?
因为尊重
Respect.
对你 以及这个部门的尊重
For you and the office.
除非有确凿证据
And until there's evidence to the contrary,
否则就假定你是无辜的 部长女士
you'll get the benefit of the doubt, Madam Secretary.
谢谢你 Gibbs探员
Thank you, Agent Gibbs.
现在要做的事 是在信息泄露之前追查
Job now is finding who's responsible
谁对这起窃听事件负有责任
before anything leaks.
我昨天在秘密场所参加了
I had classified briefings
国防部的三场机密情报会议
at three D.O.D. off-site locations yesterday,
而且我们所探讨的部署策略
and we talked enough deployment strategy
能够对海军和海军陆战队
to cause serious security problems
造成严重的安全问题
for the sailors and Marines I work for.
请你理解 他们的安危是我唯一关心的 Gibbs探员
Understand, they are my only concern in this, Agent Gibbs.
Abby已经拿了那只窃听笔 老大
Abby's got the spy pen, boss.
根据电池容量以及剩余电量分析
Based on the battery size and the length of the charge left,
我们认为它录音了将近30个小时左右
we think it's been recording for about 30 hours or so.
我们能追踪到是谁在窃听吗
Can we track who's listening?
这不是现场直播
It's not a live feed.
窃听器只存储信息
The bug stores the data internally,
这意味着安置窃听器的人
which means whoever planted it
必须得下载这些信息
has to download the info.
我们必须假设他们已经这么做了
Which we have to assume they've already done.
好吧 我会警示五角大楼
All right, I will alert the Pentagon that my meetings
昨天的会议内容被泄露了
yesterday were compromised.
我们应该和NSA共同处理这个问题
【注：NSA 美国国家安全局】
And we should bring in the NSA.
我刚刚提出了这个请求
I just put in a request for info.
让他们时刻警惕有关出卖美国情报的问题
They got ears open for the sale of U.S. intel.
我们尽力不要让事情发展到那个地步
Let's make sure it doesn't get that far.
我跟着你做 老大
You zig, I zag, boss.
我在和NSA通电话时
While I was on the horn with NSA,
调出了一份威胁分析报告
I pulled a threat analysis report.
他们在十分钟内就做了这份报告吗
They put this together in the last ten minutes?
不 这报告在两年前就完成了
No. The paper's two years old.
但是它准确地预言了我们这次的泄露事件
But it predicts our breach exactly.
"秘密录音装置"
"Clandestine recording device,
"高级别的政府官员"
"high-level government official,
"一件日常用品
"an everyday item
例如一支钢笔"
such as an ink pen."
巧合吗
Coincidence?
我们得和写这份报告的人谈一谈
We need to talk to the person who wrote this paper.
我还以为要经过全面细致地搜身才能进来这里呢
I thought we were gonna get a cavity search coming in here.
真有趣
Interesting.
嗯
Hmm.
哇 看那里
Whoa, look at that.
我们最好别告诉McGee 这里有《星际迷航》游戏里的椅子
We better not tell McGee about the Star Trek video game chairs.
他会疯了的
It'll just irritate him.
这儿就像是苹果直营店
It's like an Apple Store.
你们一定是NCIS吧
You must be NCIS.
欢迎来到国家安全操控中心
Welcome to the National Security Operations Center.
我是NSA特别探员 Chad Flynderling
I'm NSA Special Agent Chad Flynderling.
你们可以叫我Flynn
You can call me Flynn.
Flynn
Flynn.
就像电影《创战纪》里的Jeff Bridges吗
【注：在电影中Jeff Bridges饰演的角色名叫Kevin Flynn】
Like Jeff Bridges in Tron?
真新颖啊
That's original.
抱歉
Sorry. I'm sorry.
我现在对NSA的公众认知度很敏感
I'm sensitive to NSA's public perception right now.
我们可不是一群不问世事 只懂数据的书呆子
We're not just a bunch of reclusive data nerds.
我们的员工就像这里的工作一样 多种多样
Our employees are as diverse as the work that we do here.
而且我发誓 要是我再听到
And I swear,if I have to hear another crack
一句关于《星际迷航》椅子的笑话...
about the Star Trek chairs...
嘿 看那些
Oh, hey, look at those.
根本就没注意到哎
Didn't even notice them.
我重新读了你所说的那份威胁分析报告
I reviewed the threat report you called about.
-是你写的吗 -不是
- You write it? - Well, no.
不过我可以协助你
Uh, but I can assist you with anything you might need.
我们需要见报告的原作者
We asked for the original author.
就这么办 一号
【注；《星际迷航》中Picard船长的口头禅】
Make it so, Number One.
有什么问题吗
What's the problem?
呃...
Uh...
关于我提及的那些不问世事的数据书呆子...
About those reclusive data freaks I was talking about...
这情况会持续多久
So how long does this go on?
稍等一下
Yeah, just wait for it.
Gibbs探员 DiNozzo探员
Uh, Agents Gibbs and DiNozzo,
这是我们NSA的分析员
give you NSA Analyst
Ellie Bishop
Ellie Bishop.
她喜欢在这里做一些
She prefers to do her
非机密的研究工作
unclassified research in here.
我们讨论过第一条规定的 Flynn
I thought we discussed rule number one, Flynn.
如果我带着耳机 就闪一下台灯
When my earbuds are in, flash the desk light.
我也是没办法
Couldn't help it.
我是Bishop
Bishop.
很高兴见到你
It's good to meet you.
不好意思 我正在处理一些...事情
Sorry, I was in the middle of... stuff.
对 这是我写的 怎么了
Yup. That's my work. What's up?
你连看都没看
You didn't even look at it.
这是我进NSA上班的第三天写的
I wrote it my third day at the NSA.
一个星期三的早晨
It was a Wednesday morning.
我刚吃完一盒可可麦片
I just finished a box of Cocoa Pebbles.
我记得这些 是因为
I remember that because it was
包装盒里的礼物给了我撰写报告的灵感
the prize inside the box that inspired the entire paper.
让我猜猜 一支钢笔
Let me guess. A pen?
一件隐藏在眼皮底下的日常用品
An everyday object hiding in plain sight.
就这样有了灵感
It clicked.
所以 你通过一个早餐麦片的盒子
So you got 25 pages of national security strategy
写下了25页有关国家安全策略的报告
from inside a breakfast cereal?
为了更好地应对袭击
In order to better prepare for attacks,
我会假想还没有发生的威胁
I dream up threats that haven't happened yet.
你的假想成真了
This dream came true.
所以我是对的
So I was right.
海军部长身上被装了窃听器
Secretary of the Navy was bugged.
安全情报陷入危机
Security intel is at risk.
这太糟糕了
Which is bad.
但是我把报告提交给上司
But I submit my reports to my superiors,
他们再将那些报告分发给各个部门
who then distribute them accordingly.
任何有基本安全权限的人都可以阅读
Anyone with basic security clearance could have access.
你给别人看过这份报告吗
Did you give this paper to anybody else?
没有
No.
你是在问我是否跟窃听事件有关系吗
Are you asking if I'm in on it or something?
呃 我没有 我...
Uh, no, I-I'm not, I...
我写剧本
I wrote the playbook, but I have
但我不知道谁在付诸行动
no idea who's running it.
对不起
Sorry.
希望你们能找到那个人
Hope you find your guy.
很高兴见到你们
It was nice to meet you.
像我说的
Like I said,
她不是一个外勤探员
she's not a field agent.
我能听见你说话 Jeff Daniels
【注：美国演员 出演美剧《新闻编辑室》里的主播】
I can still hear you, Jeff Daniels.
Jeff Daniels不在《创战纪》里
Jeff Daniels wasn't in Tron.
应该是Jeff Bridges
That was Jeff Bridges.
Flynn 你的确是粉丝
Flynn, you are a fan.
什么事 Duck
Yeah, Duck?
嗯 我们这就回去
Yep, we're on our way back.
我们发现了另一支窃听笔
We have got a second pen.
我想这意味着
So I guess this means
-我得跟你们一起回去 -不
- I'm riding with you guys.- No.
她跟我们一起走
No, but she is.
什么 为什么
What? Why?
因为 就像你说的
'Cause, like you said,
你写了这个剧本 是吧
you wrote the playbook, right?
我们在这里干什么
What are we doing here?
我在等Ducky 我们的M.E
I'm waiting for Ducky, our M.E.
就是法医
That stands for "medical examiner."
我不是第一次参与案件
This isn't my first case.
我是说 我在这里干什么
I meant, what am I doing here?
我分析全方位的数据
I analyze big-picture data,
在全球反恐战争中提供详细的策略
present detailed strategies in the global war on terror.
或许得花很多年才能真正落实的棋局
Chess moves that can take years to implement.
你喜欢玩棋盘游戏
You enjoy playing board games?
听着 我所能告诉你的一切都在那份报告里
Look, everything I can offer you is in that report.
我本人在这里能起什么作用
What good can I do in person?
我不知道 但是你可以
I don't know,but you can start
开始读这份卷宗 赶上我们的进度
by catching up on the case file.
没错
Yes.
那你能告诉我要多长时间吗
Well, then, can you tell me how long?
我当然能等
Of course I can hold on.
我觉得你不是FBI 也不是来告诉我
I don't suppose you're from the FBI and you've come to tell me
整件事情都是误会
that all this is a misunderstanding?
不好意思 我来自NSA 名叫...
Sorry, NSA. My name...
这毫不相干
That is totally irrelevant.
10分钟之前我还跟他说过话
I was just talking to the man ten minutes ago.
特区法医在躲我的电话
The D.C. M.E. is dodging my calls.
Duck 我以为这是关于另一个窃听器
Duck, I thought this was about another bug,
-而不是一具尸体 -两者皆是
- not a body.- It's both.
多亏了我们的搜查令 法医重新检查
Thanks to our BOLO, the M.E. found a second pen
他的个人物品时 发现了第二只钢笔
when he went back through this man's personal effects.
他是Claude Sherman
He's Claude Sherman,
优耐电子公司的会计师
accountant for United Equinox Electronics.
是的 他就职于
Yeah, he worked
今早出现在MTAC的公司之一
for one of the companies in MTAC this morning.
谋杀
Murder?
不 自然死亡
No, natural causes.
两天前死于心肌梗塞
Myocardial infarction two days ago.
Ducky 为什么他出现在这里
Ducky, then what's he doing here?
尸体和个人物品一起运送
Body and personal effects travel together
以保证证据的完整性
in order to preserve the chain of evidence.
我说过 这不是我的第一个案子
Like I said,this is not my first case.
等一下
Stop.
-Ducky 钢笔在哪里 -不见了
- Ducky, where's the pen? - It's missing.
所以我整个早晨都在打电话
That's why I've been on the phone all morning.
根据
Yeah, according
法医办公室的说法
to the M.E.'s office,
一位FBI探员在09:15转运之前
an FBI agent collected the personal effects
搜集了所有的个人物品
just before the transfer at 0915.
问题在于 当我打电话确认的时候
The problem is,when I called to confirm,
这位FBI根本就不知道这件事情
the FBI doesn't know anything about it.
-有人假冒FBI探员 -看来就是这样
- Somebody posing as an agent. - It would appear so.
给我们留下一具尸体和更多的疑问
Leaving us a body and more questions.
谁偷了这只钢笔
Who stole the pen?
跟在海军部长身上装窃听器的
Was it the same person who planted it
是同一个人吗
on SECNAV?
有什么联系呢
What's the connection?
不好意思 你的名字是什么
I'm sorry...what was your name again?
Bishop
Bishop.
你想到些什么
You got something?
呃 也许
Yeah, uh, maybe.
你这里有吃的吗
You got any food around here?
什么都行
Anything?
总能找到些东西 走吧
We'll find stuff. Come on.
五角大楼拒绝透露 海军部长参加的情报会议记录
Pentagon refuses to release any of the minutes
from SECNAV's briefings.
一旦情报泄露 整个世界都会知道
Once the intel leaks, the whole world will know.
我就是这么跟他们说的
Yeah, it's what I told them,
但他们仅能透露的是 讨论的话题
except all they could say was, topics of discussion
包括俄罗斯 中国 叙利亚跟伊朗
included Russia, China, Syria and Iran.
真是缩小了范围啊
That narrows it down.
是啊
Yeah.
就是她
That her?
她摔倒了吗
She fall down?
哦 别被这里的一片混乱蒙蔽了
Oh, uh, don't let the chaos fool you.
这只是我的工作方式
This is just how I work.
好吧 Jeff Goldblum
【注：美国演员 出演过电影《变蝇人》】
All right, Jeff Goldblum,
有人在海军部长身上装了窃听器
guy plants a bug on SECNAV,
上传了数据
uploads the data.
他用来做什么呢
What's he do with it?
你说
Go.
你读过我的报告吗
Did you read my paper?
看了一点 但是我...
Some... some of it, but I...
时间很紧迫 而且我...
Time is a factor here,and I...
那是婚戒吗 你结婚了
Is that a wedding ring? Are you married?
今晚我会把报告给你 可以吗
I'll have my report to you by tonight, okay?
-报告 -嗯
- Report? - Mm-hmm.
今晚
Tonight?
等等 我从头理一下
Wait, let's back the truck up.
你多大了
How old are you?
嘿 不是说时间很紧迫吗
Ha.I thought time was a factor around here.
讨论我的个人生活不是浪费时间吗
Isn't talking about my personal life a waste of it?
-不是 -是
- No. - Yes.
在我看来 窃听的人有三个选择
Well, the way I see it, our guy has three options.
第一 他把这些
One: he releases
信息全部泄露
the information in the name of full disclosure.
那我们应该已经听到风声了
Which he would have already done.
第二 他把这些信息卖给敌人
Two: he sells the data to the enemy.
但是他事先并不知道
Except he had no way of knowing
窃听到的会是什么情报
what kind of intel the bug would record.
-需要找到正确的买家 -这会花很多时间
- Needs to find the right buyer. - Which takes time.
剩下第三个选择
Leaving us with option three:
他把信息反过来卖给我们
he sells the information back to us.
勒索
Extortion.
额 等一下 这...这仅仅是个猜测
Yeah, uh, wait, tha-that...that was just a guess.
我们需要提醒海军部长办公室
We need to alert the SECNAV's office
这个人可能会打电话
this guy might be calling.
-他已经打了 -勒索
- He just did. - Extortion?
记时已经开始
Clock's already started.
中午12:30 海军部长办公室
12:30 p.m., SECNAV's office was contacted
收到一封加密邮件
via an encrypted e-mail.
我们有一个小时的时间 将一千万
We have one hour to deposit $10 million
存到一个离岸账户 不然他就泄露情报
【注：在境外银行开立的账户 客户可以从离岸账户上自由调拨资金而不受本国的外汇管制】
into an offshore account or he leaks the intel.
我们能追踪这个邮件吗
Can we track the communication?
不行 幕后之人
No, who's ever behind this knows their way
懂计算机代码 也知道如何隐藏行踪
around computer code and knows how to hide.
我们有多大几率
What are the chances
能在一小时内抓住这个家伙
of catching this guy before the deadline?
如果直接把钱付给他 几率会更高
Well, they get better if we just pay him.
-给他想要的 -不
- Give the man what he wants.- No.
我们可不喜欢
We don't like
给恐怖分子任何东西
giving terrorists anything,
更不用说是纳税人的钱
much less taxpayer money.
我也是 但是就像我在NSA告诉上司的那样
Neither do I,but like I told my boss at NSA,
这是做生意必须付出的代价
it's the cost of doing business.
如果我们往账户里存了钱
If we deposit the money into the account
而他进入账户 我们就有机会追踪他
and he accesses it, it gives us something to trace.
在我的报告里都概述过了
It's all outlined in my paper.
有可能我们的间谍正用同一份报告
Would that be the same paper our spy
作为他的行动步骤
could be using as a paint-by-numbers?
他知道这是我们的策略
He'll know that's our strategy.
就算没有报告 他也早就猜到了
He would have guessed it anyway,
我们可以用NSA的编码去破解他的
which makes it our NSA codes against his.
从统计学上看 这对我们更有利
And statistically,the odds are in our favor.
这是我们找到他的最好办法
It's our best way of finding him.
数据统计不会说谎
Statistics don't lie.
-对 但坏人会 -撒谎
- Yeah, but our bad guy might.- Lie?
-关于什么 -我们不知道
- About what?- We don't know
关于他的任何信息 或者他到底想要什么
anything about him or what he wants.
他想要钱 对吧
He wants money, right?
除非他还想要更多
Unless he hasn't shown his full hand.
继续搜查 直到我们找到他
Keep digging till we find it.
这根本...根本说不通
That doesn't...doesn't make sense.
有些时候你得相信直觉
Sometimes you got to go with your gut.
好吧 但和直觉相比 我想我们都同意
Sure, but gut logic aside, I think we can all agree here
这种情况下 遵循逻辑更好
that actual logic is better.
我们马上就能知道了
Well, we're about to find out.
海军部长刚刚同意了
SECNAV just approved
Bishop的计划
Bishop's game plan.
让NSA来牵头汇款行动
Gave NSA the lead on the money-drop.
Porter有话要跟我们说 Gibbs
Porter wants to have a word with us, Gibbs.
好样的
Good.
同样的监听装置
The same kind of surveillance device
出现在我公司的会计身上
was found on my corporate accountant.
我没有在你的雇员身上
I didn't plant
放置窃听器
a bug on your employee,
而且我也绝对没有
and I sure as hell didn't plant a bug
在海军部长的身上放置窃听器
on the Secretary of the Navy!
你胆大包天 竟敢指控我犯叛国罪
You got stones accusing me of treason.
互相责怪是没有用的
There's no sense pointing fingers.
别假装是个爱国者了 Ward
Quit playing the patriot, Ward.
我是一个爱国者 我的公司为这个军队服务了四代人
I am a patriot. My company's been serving this military for four generations.
我们可不是什么发战争财的公司
We're not some startup war profiteer.
够了
That's enough.
我知道你们都担心
I understand you're concerned
公司机密被泄露
about corporate secrets being leaked.
即使没有任何泄露
Even if nothing leaks,
像这样的话传出去也会让我的公司倒闭
word of this would kill me on Wall Street.
我们讨论的是上亿的金钱
We're talking hundreds of millions.
我们正在追踪那个从你员工身上找到的监听器 Marc
We are following up on the device found on your employee, Marc,
但你得给我们一点时间来做我们的工作
but give us time to do our jobs.
我可以向你们俩保证
I can assure you both
我们最好的探员正在日以继夜地工作
that our best agents are working on this around the clock.
对不对 Gibbs探员
Isn't that right, Agent Gibbs?
哦 我确定你刚刚让我们都出局了 长官
Oh, I'm pretty sure you just took us off the clock, ma'am.
先生们 失陪一下
Gentlemen, if you'll excuse me for a moment.
我因为这件事情承受着各方压力
I'm getting hit on all sides with this--
五角大楼 白宫
Pentagon, White House.
人们不需要另一个情报丑闻
【注：指斯诺登的棱镜门】
Last thing anybody needs is another intel scandal,
而且NSA对这种威胁有所防备
and NSA is prepared for this kind of threat.
我们也是 部长女士
So are we, Madam Secretary.
我希望你能继续以往出色的工作 Leon
And I want you to keep up the good work, Leon.
我不是把你当成候补 只是在增加更多的人手
I'm not benching you; I'm just adding more players to the game.
术业有专攻
Different players have different strengths.
是的 而作为总指挥 我要根据我的方法来编排阵容 主任
Yes, and as head coach, I have the lineup just the way I want it, Director.
尔等明白了吗
Is that understood?
每一个人都在盯着
Everybody's looking
一个没有军事背景的女性海军部长
at a female SECNAV with no military background,
疑心这两点
wondering if either one of those things
会不会造成问题
are gonna be a factor.
我希望能够妥善处理此事 让他们瞧瞧
I'd like to answer them by setting this right.
因此 我需要得到所有的帮助
And to do that, I need all the help I can get.
尤其是你们的
Especially yours.
哦 天啊
Oh, God.
愚蠢的笔 给我答案吧
Stupid pen, give me answers.
你在那儿站了多久了
How long have you been standing there?
哦 几分钟罢了
Oh, just a few minutes.
-我以为你知道的 -我不知道
- I thought you knew. - No.
但是你跟我说话来着
But you were talking to me.
不 我是在跟我自己 还有一支...笔说话
No, I-I was talking to myself and a... pen.
但是现在起我不会再说了
But now I'm not talking anymore,
谁知道有谁在偷听
cause who knows who's listening?
你觉得谁在偷听
Who do you think's listening?
哦 不...不要相信你听说过的任何事情
Oh, no... don't believe everything you hear.
我们不会随便地监听对话和电话
I mean, we don't randomly listen to conversations and phone calls.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
像你们一样 我们监听也需要法院指令
We need a court order just like you.
我们中确实有一些坏家伙
We've had a few bad apples,
但我们是好人
but we're good people
维护法律 作出改变
out to uphold the law and make a difference.
所以你没有监听我的电话
So you haven't bugged my phone?
听着 我可以证明 我来这里只是为了帮忙
Look, I can prove I'm here to help.
关于那个冒牌FBI探员 根据特区法医的描述 我画了这个
I drew this using D.C. examiner's description of our bogus FBI agent,
在NSA的数据库里搜索了一下 查到了一个叫Rudolph Stalin的人
fed it into the NSA database, and got a hit on a guy named Rudolph Stalin.
Rudolph Stalin
好的
Okay.
Rudolph Stalin是一个美国公民
Rudolph Stalin is an American citizen
他以前当过国际间谍
with a history of international espionage
而且和俄国有很深的政治关系
and strong political ties to Russia.
还留着非常不错的小胡子
【注：俄国人比较喜欢留小胡子】
And a very nice mustache.
我不知道这是否意在讽刺
I wonder if it's supposed to be ironic.
我们监视他将近一年了
He's been on our radar for about a year.
啊哈 而且他是一个美国公民
Aha, hmm, and he is an American citizen.
这正是为什么我们需要法院指令
Which is exactly why we needed a court order.
我记得我几个月前读过他的档案
I remember reading his file a few months ago
那时我在喝一碗奶油蘑菇汤
over a bowl of cream of mushroom soup.
我用食物来联想记忆
I-I food-associate.
哦
Oh.
我只是...只是很惊讶你会画画
I-I'm just... I'm still stuck on the fact that you can draw.
我是说 虽然画得没有Kate好 但还是非常不错
I mean, this isn't Kate good, but it's good good.
谁是Kate
Who's Kate?
那要花几个小时
That-that would take a few hours
和一整盒纸巾来讲述
and a whole box of tissues.
好吧 我们应该先发布通缉令
Okay, well, then we should get this BOLO out first,
而且我想查查NSA那边进展得如何了
and I wanted to check up on the NSA operation.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
嘿 Gibbs 你知道Bishop会画画吗
Hey, Gibbs, did you know that Bishop can draw?
是的 她还在这儿
Yeah, she's still here.
为什么
Why?
好的
Okay.
Abby
Abby?
怎么了 是不是有关汇款的事
What? Is it about the money-drop?
也许我们应该谈一谈Kate
Maybe we should have that talk about Kate.
经理听到了枪声 报了警
Manager heard the shots, called the police.
没人看到开枪的人
Nobody saw the shooter.
NSA汇了那笔勒索费
NSA deposited the extortion money,
然后我们的间谍通过咖啡店的无线网络接收
and our spy accessed it using the coffee shop's Wi-Fi.
这可不是我会接收一千万美元的最佳地点
It's not the first place I'd come to collect $10 million.
Flynderling探员也这么想
Agent Flynderling thought the same thing.
所以他没来得及呼叫支援 就先进行跟踪
That's why he came to follow up before calling in a task force.
三次近距离枪杀 正中胸部
Three gunshot wounds to the chest at close range.
根据弹孔的火药残留和身体组织的损伤程度
Based on the stippling and tissue damage,
他没有还手的机会
he never had a chance.
刚刚才从他的汽车里出来
Barely got out of his car.
-伏击 -老大
- Ambushed. - Boss,
他的口袋里有东西
he's got something in his pocket.
嘿 老大 这不是她的...
Hey, boss, isn't this her...
我的报告
My report.
你是对的 Gibbs探员
You were right, Agent Gibbs.
这和那个无关 Bishop
It's not about that, Bishop.
有人在海军部长的身上放置了监听器
Somebody plants a surveillance device on the Secretary of the Navy,
敲诈了美国政府
and extorts the U.S. Government.
很可能和在特区验尸房里偷第二支监听笔的冒牌FBI探员是同一个人
Likely the same guy who posed as an FBI agent to steal a second spy pen from the D.C. morgue.
Rudolph Stalin--
他因把美国情报出售给俄罗斯人而被通缉
he's an American wanted for selling U.S. intel to Russia.
有着那样的名字和那样的小胡子
【注：Stalin这名字让人联想到苏联大元帅Joseph Stalin】
With a name and a mustache like that,
我真是震惊啊
I... I'm shocked.
但是当NSA试图
But when the NSA tried
汇款给他并追踪那笔存款时
to pay him off and track the deposit...
他杀了NSA的Flynderling探员
He murdered NSA Agent Flynderling
而且拿着那笔钱逃之夭夭
and got away with the money.
事实上 我刚查了下离岸账户
Actually, I just checked the offshore account.
那笔勒索费还在
The extortion money's still there.
他没动那一千万美元
He left behind ten million bucks.
-这没有道理 -可能是杀了人之后吓坏了
- doesn't make any sense. - Could've panicked after the shooting.
也许这家伙没有我们想的那么专业
Maybe this guy's not as professional as we thought.
或者 这从一开始就与勒索山姆大叔无关
【注：山姆大叔就是美国政府】
Or maybe it's not about Uncle Sam's money in the first place.
通过诱杀一个联邦探员 Stalin还可以得到什么
What... what else does Stalin get by luring and killing a federal agent?
证明 向另一个买家证明
Authentication. Proof to another buyer
这个情报是真的
that his intel is genuine.
有人愿意支付超过一千万美元
Somebody willing to pay more than ten mil.
所以他利用了我们
So he used us?
这家伙在下棋 而我竟然从来没发现
This guy was playing chess, and I never even saw it.
我知道我要做什么
I know what I have to do.
清零
Reset.
我会重新来一遍
I'll start over.
-Bishop. -这次我能够查出来的
- Bishop. - I'll get it this time.
我只是需要一些时间来清理棋盘
I just need some time to clear the chessboard.
Bishop
Bishop.
休息一下
Take a break.
去买瓶饮料
Go get a soda.
没有时间 而且我没零钱
There's no time, and I have no cash.
拿着
Take it.
是的 Abbs
Yeah, Abbs?
-你可以来我的实验室吗 -可以
- Can you come to my lab? - Yep.
米开朗基罗 莎士比亚 达芬奇 海明威
Michelangelo, Shakespeare, da Vinci, Hemingway.
今天 你可以把我的名字加入他们的行列了 Gibbs
Today, you can count me amongst their ranks, Gibbs.
-我每天都这么干的 Abbs -你查到了什么
- I do every day, Abbs. - What do you got?
一个大师级的线索
A masterpiece.
看起来像是一个日期和时间
Well, it looks like a date and time stamp.
有的时候 最伟大的艺术作品往往最简单
Sometimes the greatest works of art are simple.
-你搞定这支笔了 -没 我失败了
- You got into the pen? - No. I failed.
内置的存储芯片加密得实在太好了
The internal memory chip was too well encrypted.
那这是什么 Abbs
Then what is this, Abbs?
这是通过无线传感器登陆这个芯片的最后日期和时间
That is the last day and time the chip was accessedby the Wi-Fi transmitter
啊 就是芯片的发送端
Ah. That the send-y part?
是的
Yes.
所以 我不能告诉你
So, I can't tell you
我们的坏家伙从这支笔里下载了什么
what our bad guy downloaded from the pen,
但是 因为芯片的发送端
but, because of the send-y part,
我可以告诉你他什么时候下载的
I can tell you when he did it.
是的 昨天
Yeah. Yesterday.
晚上7:23
7:23 p.m.
假设那支笔那时仍在海军部长的口袋里
And assuming that SECNAV still had the pen in her pocket--
我交叉检查了她的时间表
I cross-referenced her schedule.
Stalin下载时 Porter正和她十几岁的女儿在一个餐厅吃饭
Porter was at a restaurant having dinner with her teenage daughter when Stalin was downloading.
他需要有多近
How close would he have to be?
非常近 这是一支很小的笔 很短的天线
Close. It's a small pen-- small antenna.
所以我检查了餐厅附近街道的监控录像
So I pulled street surveillance footage from near the restaurant,
然后发现Stalin坐在他的车里
and found Stalin sitting in his car,
正犯着叛国罪
committing high treason.
我猜到处都有耳目确实挺有帮助
I guess having eyes and ears everywhere can be helpful.
但是不要告诉Bishop我说过这话
But don't tell Bishop I said that.
车牌
License plate.
已经加到通缉令里了 Gibbs
Already added to the BOLO, Gibbs.
我们找到这家伙的几率
Our chances of finding this guy
突然加速剧增了
just skyrocketed.
Abbs 非常出色
Abbs, that's really great work.
节哀顺变
I'm sorry for your loss.
被杀的那个探员 是你的朋友吗
The agent who was killed-- was he a friend of yours?
更像是我的哥哥
More like an older brother.
一切都还好吗
Everything okay?
不能告诉家人我在做什么是很痛苦的
It's tough not being able to talk to my family about what I do.
你应该看看 当我告诉我妈
You should've seen my mom when I told her
我在俄克拉荷马州外工作时她的表情
I was taking a job outside of Oklahoma.
那你为什么说了
Why did you?
嗯 那就是妈妈和爸爸之间的区别
Mm. That's the difference between Mom and Dad.
他的第一条规矩就是 舒适使人安逸
His first rule is: comfort makes for complicity.
意为只有不断挑战自己才能成长
Means the only way to grow is by challenging yourself.
的确 这有助于记住我们工作的原因
Well, it helps to remember why we do the job.
让自己不断前进
Keeps us going.
事实上 我该回NSA了
Actually, I should get back to NSA.
嗯 你可没那么容易溜走
Mm. You're not getting off that easy.
Gibbs也喜欢规矩 第45条
Gibbs likes rules, too. Number 45:
自己清理自己的烂摊子
always clean up your mess.
-怎么清理 -这个嘛 首先
- How? - Well, for starters,
Rudolph Stalin的通缉令有回应了
the BOLO came back on Rudolph Stalin.
我们知道他在哪了
We know where he is.
走吧 没时间浪费了
Come on. Time's a-wastin'.
好的 谢谢
Okay, thanks.
特区警署说Stalin的汽车
Metro PD says Stalin's car
仍旧停在前面很远的地方
is still parked in a lot out front.
他们不确定他在哪个放映厅
They're not sure which theater he's in,
不过一共就两个厅 你们想要我去哪儿
but there are only two screens. Where do you want me?
我在武器与外勤训练中成绩拔尖
I aced my weapons and field training.
你有枪吗 Ado Annie
【注：歌剧《俄克拉荷马人》里的一个人物】
You got a gun, Ado Annie?
我把它留在我的四轮马车上了
I left it in my surrey with the fringe on top.
别对我引用《俄克拉荷马人》
Don't quote Oklahoma to me.
呆在车里
Stay in the car.
没问题
You bet.
他
Him.
就是他
That's him!
联邦探员
Federal agent!
站住 站住 站住
Stop, stop, stop!
Bishop 你为什么用车撞他
Bishop, why'd you hit him with the car?
事实上 是他撞到车上的
Well... technically, he ran into the car.
必须说 那是凭直觉的 直觉是好事 对吗
Got to say, that was a gut move. Gut's good, right?
我们故意让这家伙跑出来的
We intentionally flushed the guy out.
Gibbs一直都守在出口
Gibbs had the exit covered the whole time.
什么
What?
她在刚刚那一瞬间变成Palmer了 老大
She pulled a Palmer on this guy, boss.
至少他会安静地和我们回去
At least he'll go quietly.
除非有律师在 否则我什么都不会说
I'm not saying anything without a lawyer.
你们用车撞了我
You hit me with a car.
我以为他要逃跑
I thought he was getting away.
我读了他的档案 他在高中时是个田径明星
I read in his file that he was a high school track star.
我能够记得我读的几乎所有东西
I remember almost everything I read.
其中包括很多审讯记录
Which includes more than a few interrogation transcripts.
言外之意是
Meaning what?
我有一个主意
I have an idea.
等一下 这些
Hang on. These.
什么
What?
我需要借用这个
I need to borrow this.
谢谢
Thank you.
审讯最重要的原则就是
Now, a major principle of an interrogation
让嫌疑人自己下结论 是吧
is to let the suspect draw their own conclusions, right?
所以 只要我不说自己是他的律师
Which means, as long as I never say I'm his lawyer,
他也不问的话...
as long as he never asks...
站住
Stop.
我能做到
I can keep up.
在你撞到他之前 他看见你没有
Did that guy see you before you hit him?
没有
Mm-mm.
我们已经打电话给公共辩护处...
Look, we called the public defender...
嗨 你...
Hey. What...
终于来了 你是我的...
Finally. Are you my...?
不好意思我穿成这样
Sorry for the outfit.
今天本该我休假的 我是Ellie Bishop
Today was supposed to be my day off. Ellie Bishop.
你问过他问题吗
Have you been asking him questions?
从法律上讲 我们有权
Legally, we can ask
想问多少就问多少
as many questions as we want.
由犯罪嫌疑人决定要不要在无律师的情况下开口
Up to the suspect to talk without a lawyer.
说的没错 你想开口吗
That's true.Do you want to talk?
我们是不是应该先私下谈谈 或者...
Shouldn't we speak somewhere in private first? Or...
由你决定 我已经看过了相关文件
It's up to you. I mean, I've read the file,
他们这个谋杀案的确证据确凿
and they do have a pretty solid murder case.
-谋杀 -没错 一个联邦探员被杀
- Murder? - Yeah. Of a federal agent.
不可能 我 我没杀过人
No way. I-I didn't kill anybody.
他们发现了海军部长钢笔上的蹊跷
They know about the pen on the Secretary of the Navy.
他们查出你当时在餐馆
They know that you were at the restaurant,
也知道了一千万美元的事
and they know about the $10 million.
你可以坦白从宽的
You can help yourself, though.
如果你认罪的话
If you cop to the murder,
-也许可以减刑 -我没杀人
- might reduce sentencing. - I didn't kill anybody!
你朝一个联邦探员的胸口连射三枪
You shot a federal agent three times in the chest!
喂 别太激动
Hey! Take it down a peg.
他说他没杀人 好吗
He said he didn't kill anybody, okay?
-我们先听他把话说完 -那你让他快说
- Let's hear him out. - Then you make it fast.
我没有勒索政府
I did not extort the government,
我也没有杀这个探员
and I did not kill this agent.
但我知道是谁做的
But I know who did.
-名字 -Edward Gracy
- Name. - Edward Gracy.
他之前卖过情报给我
He's sold me info before.
一些技术机密之类的公司项目
Corporate stuff at tech secrets.
这是他第一次提供政府情报
This is the first time he's offered government intel.
所以你承认了叛国
So you're admitting to treason.
我们该信他的话吗
We supposed to believe this?
我不知道要不要相信他
I don't know if I believe him at all.
需要他的地址来证明你说的话
Need an address to prove it.
写吧
Here you go.
我的控辩协议怎么办
Hey, what about my deal?
这事你得跟你的律师商量
Oh, you'll have to take that up with your lawyer.
你说过你是我的律师
You said you were my lawyer.
不 我没说过 我给了你名片
No, I didn't. Gave you my card.
这在法庭上能站得住脚吗
Is that gonna hold up in court?
我不知道 我也不是律师
I don't know.I'm not a lawyer, either.
好了 确认是城内一处办公室
All right, got confirmation on a downtown office,
承租者名为Edward Gracy
rent in the name Edward Gracy.
我已经通知了特区警署 他们严阵以待
I alerted Metro PD, and they're on standby.
我正在适应这里的节奏
Getting used to your pace here.
那你会需要这个的
Well, then you're gonna need this.
呃...这东西之前有人穿过吗
Uh... h-has this been used?
我是Bishop
Bishop.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
当然
Of course.
是...是的
Y... Yes.
是的 马上
Yes, right away.
出什么事了 特区警署出状况了
What's the matter? There a problem with Metro?
不是 是我在NSA的上司
No. Uh, it was my boss at NSA.
他们要我立刻回总部汇报
They need me back at HQ to debrief immediately.
要出发了
Got to go.
联邦探员
Federal agents!
Edward Gracy
Edward Gracy!
没人在
Nobody's home.
你怎么想 我们又被耍了么
What do you think? We being played again?
检查一下桌子
Check the desk.
没什么有用的 只有些垃圾邮件
Nothing here but junk mail,
GSM的过期杂志
back issues of GSM.
都是寄到这儿给Edward Gracy的
They're all addressed here to Edward Gracy.
噢
Oh.
这就是我们的幕后弈者
This is our master chess player?
老大 我查到点东西
Boss, I got something back here.
这绝对是Gracy制造窃听器的地方
Well, this is definitely where Gracy makes his bugs,
而且显然还提高对心脏疾病的关注率
and apparently raises awareness about heart disease, as well.
慈善机构信函
Charity mailers?
-难道凶手很有善心 -不
- Our killer has a conscience? - Nope.
是他的目标有善心
His targets do.
寄给海军部长Sarah Porter的邮递收据
Shipping receipt for a mailer sent to Sarah Porter.
他把窃听器
SECNAV. He's sending the bugs
和宣传单一起寄出
with the brochures.
垃圾邮件 免费赠品
Junk mail free gifts.
并非回邮地址标签
Instead of return-address labels,
你得到一支超级间谍笔
you get a super spy pen?
这可是很大风险 甚至无法保证
It's a big risk with no guarantee
这支笔能够通过你的"废品匣" 更不用说进入MTAC了
it's gonna make it past your junk drawer, let alone MTAC.
这儿全都是收据
This is full of receipts.
他定时发送这些邮件
He sends them out like clockwork.
都来自于相同的邮局
These are all from the same post office.
喂
Hello.
你在这儿做什么
What the hell are you doing here?
呃...
Uh...
我可以解释
Okay, I can explain.
我深入调查Edward Gracy这个名字
I kept digging into the name Edward Gracy.
我只是...我控制不住自己
I just...I couldn't help myself.
回你的车上去
Get back in your car.
好的 但等一下 Gracy这个名字是化名
Okay, but wait. Th-The name Gracy is an alias,
我查到了一张仍在使用的信用卡 每周都有固定的消费
and I found an open credit card with weekly purchases...
-Bishop -就是在这个邮局
- Bishop! - ...a-at this post office, okay?
我是来这里
I-I came here
追查线索的
to follow up.
Gracy的邮箱就在这里面
Gracy's P.O. box is inside the store.
我知道 他也在里面
I know! So is he.
这是我一直想告诉你的
It's what I'm trying to tell you.
噢
Oh.
你在监视他
You're on a stakeout.
-老大 -Bishop
- Boss? - Bishop!
快开车
Go!
你在书里读到怎么让坏人缴械投降的吗
What, did you read a book on disarming bad guys?
我有三个哥哥 别挣扎了
Three older brothers. Quit squirming!
我想我们会发现这把枪
I think we'll find this weapon's
和谋杀Flynn的武器相符
a match to the one that killed Flynn.
我来接手吧
I'll take it from here.
-可以了么 -是的
- You got it? - Yeah.
好的
All right.
我们走吧 大块头
Here we go, big guy.
怎么了
What?
我们都是对的
We were both right.
我们抓到了他
And we got him.
你还是没看到重点 Bishop
You're still missing the point, Bishop.
指纹显示这个人
Got a hit on the fingerprint.
真名是Thaddeus Knox
Real name is Thaddeus Knox.
因从事商业间谍活动受到多项指控
Multiple arrests for corporate espionage.
现在又加上叛国罪和谋杀罪
Now we can add treason and murder.
-这说不通啊 -又怎么了 Russell Crowe
【注：好莱坞男星 主演过角斗士】
- It doesn't make any sense. - What now, Russell Crowe?
你的美丽心灵
【注：2001年出品的电影 讲述数学家John Nash的一生】
Hasn't your beautiful mind
今天还没让你吃够苦头
gotten you in enough trouble today?
找到答案前我是不会退出的
Look, I don't quit until I get it right, and our corporate
我们这位开公司的花样美男并不符合测写
pretty boy just doesn't fit into the big picture.
无论是NSA还是NCIS都没有见过他
We've never seen him--NSA or NCIS.
-他是个新手 -没错
- He's a first-timer. - Exactly.
如果他一向把窃听器
But if he sends bugs to tech employees
寄给科技公司的雇员来窃取商业秘密的话 为什么突然把目标转向海军部长
looking for corporate secrets,why make the jump to SECNAV
还冒着终身监禁的风险去杀人
and a crime that carries out a life sentence?
有些事逼他离开了舒适圈
Something made him leave his comfort zone.
这跟意识形态和权力无关 是...
It's not about ideology or power, it's...
是自我挑战
it's about challenging himself,
证明他能胜任这项工作
proving that he can do the job.
他是为了讨谁的欢心呢
Who's he trying to impress?
他的老板
His boss.
对了 对了 对了 对了
Yup, yup, yup, yup.
别告诉我 你能从这些杂乱无章的邮件中找到线索
Don't tell me those crazy papers are finally paying off.
-Bishop -我有个
- Bishop... - I have staff lists
今早在MTAC里的公司的人员名单
from the corporations in MTAC this morning.
窃听器寄给了几乎所有公司的雇员 除了一家
Bugs have been sent to employees of every company except one.
-就是给Gracy付钱的那个公司 -Beringer Marine
- The same company that's paying Gracy. - Beringer Marine.
他们和海军部长有过节吗
What do they have against SECNAV?
Gibbs探员
Agent Gibbs.
你也是来听进展汇报的
You here for the update?
怎么了
What's going on?
我怎么知道
Hell if I know.
部长女士让我停止工作
Madam Secretary's cut me out of the loop.
是啊 就连我也注意到了
Yeah. I couldn't help but notice
你们俩之间的紧张气氛
the tension between you two earlier.
你知道 我不在乎接受命令
You know, I don't mind taking orders.
但我更情愿它们来自海军陆战队成员
I'd prefer they come from fellow Marines,
或者是服过兵役的人
or someone who's served.
我明白
I hear you.
一个平民发布影响数千名军官的命令
A civilian giving orders that affects thousands
真是让我难以接受
of military personnel pisses me off more than you know.
几个月前
Few months back,
我还在海军部长候选人名单上
I was on the short list for the SECNAV appointment.
我很荣幸 但我不觉得这是正确的
I was honored, but didn't feel right about it.
为什么
Why?
-你看起来资历不错 -也许吧
- You seem qualified. - Maybe.
但我从没穿过制服
But I haven't served in uniform.
而我对服过兵役的人充满敬意
And I have too much respect for those who have.
比如你
Like you.
Porter假装自己知道
It's not right
这些军人到底需要什么 这很不对
for Porter to pretend she knows what they need.
她本该做出正确选择 就像我一样
She should've done the right thing, like I did,
拒绝这个任命
and declined the position.
但是...
But...
我猜她现在不得不退位了
I guess she'll have to now.
这是什么
What is this?
NSA的窃听器
A bug at the NSA.
谁能想到呢
Who would've thought?
你背叛了我 陆战队员
You turn on me, Marine?
唯一的背叛者是你 Ward
The only turncoat here is you, Ward.
雇佣了一个商业间谍
By hiring one of your corporate spies
来为难我 你置整个国家的安危于不顾
to embarrass me, you put the entire country at risk.
我没做那种事
I had nothing to do with that.
我只想保护这个国家
I only want to protect this country
和为国效力的人民
and the people defending it.
也许我没有服过役 但我明白
I may not have served,but I know about duty
什么是职责和牺牲
and sacrifice.
军装可不足以造就整只团队
Takes more than a uniform to make a team.
Gibbs探员
Agent Gibbs?
Tony和McGee说你还在这里
Tony and McGee said you'd still be here.
是的
I am.
抱歉 这么晚还打扰你
Sorry to...bother you so late.
永远不要说抱歉
Never say you're sorry.
这是脆弱的表现
It is a sign of weakness.
我认为这是关键问题
I thought that was the point.
尤其是今天过后
Especially after today.
但我觉得我终于想通了一些东西
But I think I've finally figured something out.
你总是得找到正确答案 是吧 Bishop
You always got to have the right answer, don't you, Bishop?
很不幸 的确是的
Unfortunately.
但如果你让我说完 我能解释这为什么是错的
But if you'll let me finish, I can explain why that's wrong.
我努力工作
I work hard.
当我跌倒时 我能立刻爬起来
And when I fall,I get right back up.
我很聪明 而且我想做出改变
I'm smart, a-and I want to make a difference.
我可以做到
And I can.
我一直只顾着眼于整体的棋局
Been so busy looking at the...the chessboard on my own,
却忘了我也是其中的一份子
I... I forgot to be a part of it.
我没有表现出团队意识
I wasn't a team player.
所以...
So...
这就是我想说的
that-that's... that's what I wanted to say.
就这些
That's it.
晚安
Um, good night.
好运
Or good... good luck.
算了
Never mind.
你忘了点儿东西
You forgot something.
那不是我的
Uh, that's not mine.
你的名字在上面
It's got your name on it.
这是很多年前 我去NSA工作之前
This is my NCIS application from years ago.
向NCIS提交的工作申请
Before I took the job at NSA.
你怎么知道的
How did you know about this?
你的名字有点熟悉 我回去查了查
Your name sounded familiar;I went back and looked it up.
这就是你今天带上我的原因
That's why you brought me along today.
你也在下一盘棋
You play chess, too.
我想看看你是否还有能力应对挑战
I wanted to see if you were still up for a challenge.
为什么
Why?
我希望你留下
I'd like to keep you around.
联合工作分配
Joint duty assignment.
什么
What?
==GA字幕组==
翻译:小末 好想多点睡觉时间的冰糖 米兰伯爵 睡眠不够的小白
校对：失眠长痘的流年 佳晨就是good morning K穿学士服了 蓉小张要去旅游 lynhoo00 毯子
字幕特效/时间轴/压制：老东邪
冰糖-一到冬天就特别迷恋被窝果然这是病得治
小白-Boss你这是又要从别人那抢人的节奏？
小末-新妹纸还不错哦~~~
伯爵-史上效率最低好惆怅...
佳晨-"窃听门"还真是国际热门话题呢
蓉蓉-我的Kate呀~~~
K-毕业彩排的节奏，穿上学士服果然心情好多了
流年-冻死我了。。。
00-总觉得Gibbs和部长美阿姨眼神有暧昧
毯子-这一集真是翻译了好久。。NSA这是在努力重塑名声么？